Hey everyone, Kate here, and I've got some fantastic news.
Fish Audio has announced that they're making it free for developers starting today.
Their text-to-speech API, S2.1 Pro, supports 83 languages.
And that includes Chinese.
And they've put very few restrictions on this open access.
And there's no strict character limit.
However, it's subject to a fair-use policy.
Plus, the free trial period has been extended until the end of July.
And speaking of which, I just saw the AI rankings, and S2.1 Pro is currently in 14th place.
And its current ranking is number 14.
So, as we can see, ahead of it, we have, for example, Google's...
I've talked about Google's Flash model before.
The quality of the output is really good.
And then there's Alibaba's.
And Alibaba's TTS, whether it's the open-source or the closed-source version,
are also really good.
But what really gives Fish Audio the edge right now is that it's free.
So we can create a really great user experience.
So, I had Grok CLI build one for me as well.
An audio studio built on Fish Audio and DeepSeek.
For example, on the left side,
You can just paste a piece of text in here,
and have it generate the audio.
Or you can upload TXT files in bulk.
It will automatically apply AI optimization for you.
and then generate the audio.
Alright, so the page we're on right now is the Multi-Character Studio.
So, I'm just going to give it a piece of text here.
Then, we'll select the DeepSeek model.
You can choose either Pro or Flash.
Then, I'll click on 'AI Character Splitting'.
and it will show you what the narrator's part is down below.
And then for the different character names, their styles,
and it lays all of that out in detail.
So, in my previous tests, I found that...
So, whether I choose the Flash model or the Pro model,
I've run into issues with the AI's breakdown process.
it might miss a short phrase here and there.
So, to tackle that, I've added an AI review feature.
So, after the AI has assigned the roles,
Then I can go ahead and choose a voice from the sidebar.
So, for the voice, let's say...
And the sample texts you see here are all automatically generated by the AI.
I can click 'Preview'
And it'll play a short audio clip.
If I'm not happy with this audio,
I can just click 'regenerate'.
If you're happy with it,
then I can lock it to this character.
As you can see above the voice options, two have already been selected.
You can also use the dropdown menu to select a voice.
For example, let's select the reference ID character. Once you've picked the voice,
Then you can click 'Finalize Queue and Merge'.
Down here at the bottom of the page, you'll see a preview for each audio clip.
On the right, you can either regenerate it or download it again.
And then down here, it will automatically display them for you.
We can click to download the merged audio.
Over on the left, you can see we have a voice library.
So this voice library is what I had it generate earlier.
and save it as a voice profile.
So, these voice libraries...
So, for this one, I've already picked out a voice for a specific character before.
And right here, we can see it has a reference ID.
So just remember this.
So later on, you can just use that same ID
to generate more voices that sound just like it.
So, for example, I'll just copy this here.
Alright, let's head over to the workbench.
So, I can just select the ID and type it in.
In the text input box,
I can just type in a whole paragraph.
Click on 'AI Optimize'.
or just generate the audio directly.
And down below, the audio is generated.
Master Lin pushes the pocket watch back.
So, what if I choose to optimize it?
For example, let's say I select the Narrator mode here.
And then, let's click 'AI Optimize' one more time.
So, the AI has made two optimizations here.
It's added a tag like this before each short phrase.
Alright, so I can go ahead and click 'Generate Audio'.
This way, we can then
to process the audio in a more refined way.
The voice library also includes many system voice IDs.
You guys can also take a quick look.
And down here, you can also create a persistent clone from a sample.
In the settings, you can run a health check.
And then there's the prompt for DeepSeek.
Uh...
All of this can be modified.
So, by the time you're watching this video,
This project will be open-source.
And here are the features it has.
So now, I'm going to walk you through how to build the application we just saw.
For the planning phase, I used GPT 5.5.
and used Composer 2.5 in Grok to do the coding.
And finally, I had GPT 5.5 in Codex review the code.
So first, let's see how this plan was written.
First, I found the developer documentation for Fish Audio.
And then, I'll just paste the link directly.
and the model identifier from Fish Audio's blog post to GPT.
So, I'll have it first work with the information I've just given it.
I want to build a web UI.
and have it write the prompts for me.
So, why did I choose GPT for this task?
Because, in my opinion, GPT is currently the best at search, as you can see.
The amount of content it searches is just massive.
I also sent the same prompt to Gemini and Opus 4.8.
The plans they came up with were a lot more basic.
So, what I did next was...
So, the main thing I did was have GPT help me create this plan.
As you can see, the plan it generated is incredibly detailed.
It's packed with details.
And it includes a ton of reference links as well.
And then, it started to optimize the plan.
So, as you can see, this is the plan that GPT came up with.
There's a ton of content here, really.
For example, it outlines which documents the AI should read, the tech stack...
And the requirements for calling the Fish Audio API.
and DeepSeek AI's optimization capabilities.
The main functional module is then broken down into four parts.
And what are the cloning requirements?
And what are the requirements for the page design?
So, so many.
I wanted it to be this detailed.
The main reason is that I wanted to use Grok's /goal feature.
Of course, you can also use this feature in CC,
or in Codex.
It's super useful.
And when I say Grok CLI, I'm specifically referring to Grok Build.
If you're subscribed to SuperGrok,
Then you can use the Grok Build v0.1 model.
And there's also the Composer 2.5 model.
And it's a model that users are really loving right now.
on Cursorbench,
It's the kind of model that's not only affordable,
and super fast.
and a high-quality model at that.
And with Grok, you can directly use the Composer 2.5 fast model.
And it's super fast.
I've been really into this model lately.
And for the project I'm working on today,
In total, it used up 14% of my available Grok CLI quota.
of the monthly quota.
And by the way, I'm just on the basic SuperGrok membership.
Not the Heavy tier.
First, let me introduce the shortcut commands for Grok CLI.
And the slash commands.
So, if we want to get the most out of Grok,
That's the more convenient way to do it.
The simplest way is to just type a forward slash in its TUI.
to see the current slash commands.
You can also open the help menu for shortcuts to see the keybinds for the current version.
Because for different terminals,
so there can be some differences.
Ctrl+R lets you search your command history.
Ctrl+W deletes a word in the prompt.
So, these are some pretty essential shortcuts.
But when you're using it, you can't get away from the terminal environment.
Now, let's take a look at the official core slash commands.
For example, /resume.
/sessions and /fork are also super important.
You can also use /context to display your token usage.
Also, /btw lets you ask a question alongside the current task.
So, /question lets you ask a question alongside the current task.
This is also a really commonly used feature.
And with /rewind, you can revert to a previous state of the conversation.
And officially, Grok also provides a set of commands.
For example,
We can use /memory to activate and access its memory-related capabilities.
It also has...
Just like the /dream function in CC.
Plus, it's got some other special features.
For example, the /imagine image generation feature.
to generate images.
This is incredibly useful in app development.
Plus, it also has a video generation feature.
So, let's say you already have some skills on your computer.
You'll install it under the .agents/skills folder.
Grok will be able to find them.
Plus, there's another command called /skillify.
It can capture a session and turn it into a new skill.
And then you can solidify this entire process into a reusable...
slash commands.
The /recap command is also super useful.
It can quickly generate a dialogue.
To sum up, there's /goal.
I'll be focusing on that in a bit.
And the /export command is also fantastic.
You and Grok have had multiple conversations in this session.
So it can help you export all of that.
It also supports some headless, script-mode commands.
The -p flag is one we use pretty often.
And then there's -S, which we can use for other things.
in the AI subscription
Take Codex for example. This part is definitely something worth looking into.
Alright, now let's break down exactly how to build it.
the VOXWEAVER studio application.
This prompt...
So, this is what I was discussing with GPT 5.5 earlier.
And then I had it generate the prompt for me.
First, Grok reads the specs.
Then, it's time to build the structure, followed by the server-side, and after that, the front-end.
And of course, the front-end.
And of course, it's part of that process too.
And I was constantly testing it. This app has a three-layer architecture.
We did run into some issues along the way, though.
So, when I clicked on 'AI Optimize'...
The console threw a 500 error.
Composer quickly helped me fix it.
And it...
It diagnosed the problem and found that it was because of the JSON from DeepSeek.
was inconsistent with the project's Schema.
So, after that...
When it comes to multi-character voiceovers, there's one key thing.
and that is, how to keep the character's voice consistent.
First, I'll have it come up with a plan for me.
Then I'll pick one, and have it make the revisions.
And after the final adjustments,
Once you've selected the AI to segment the text,
In the second step, you can have the AI review it.
Then, you can preview the voice and lock it in.
Finally, you can merge all the files and download them. And after that...
And there are also a bunch of other small tweaks and modifications.
For instance, optimizing the page's performance,
speed optimization,
rules for the filenames of downloaded files, and so on.
So, for a composer,
Basically, you just give it a prompt,
And it solved it in less than a minute.
It's incredibly fast.
And the changes were spot-on.
Basically, I just sent it a few problems.
and it fixed them right away.
Later, I had Codex review the entire program.
Let's see if there are any issues.
It found a few security issues.
I took four of those issues and sent them over to Grok's Composer 2.5 model.
and had it make the fixes.
After making the changes, it also ran some tests.
Here's a part of my conversation with Grok.
The prompt I sent it.
Aside from the first prompt,
There's a lot of content in there.
Because this is a pretty complex specification document.
But other than that, the prompts were actually pretty simple.
Plus, for many of the issues, a single prompt was basically all it took.
Composer 2.5 took care of it for me.
I rarely ran into situations where we had to go back and forth.
So, it's clear that Composer 2.5 is incredibly powerful.
After that, I went ahead and made a few more modifications to the application.
But I didn't put them on the current page.
Finally, let's take a closer look at Grok.
Its /goal feature, which is the /goal command in Grok,
I just prompted it to complete the development based on a document like this one.
My default model is the Composer 2.5 fast model.
But today, while I was using Grok, I discovered something.
It's an incredible coder, seriously.
And it's also really good at checking, as you can see in this picture.
And up at the top, there's Grok.
And then, it'll show the verification.
At first, it was showing six validations.
Then it changed to nine verifications.
In its sub-agent,
We'll see there's a step called 'Verification by Grok'.
So, the function of this sub-agent is...
Its job is to verify the plan made by Grok, and the code written by Composer 2.5.
and the code it has written.
If there are any discrepancies,
it will go and revise and verify.
So, when I click on Grok,
And then, a pop-up window like this will appear.
and you can see its progress.
and what stage the review process is at.
And the prompt for this sub-agent is right above it.
This is automatically assigned by the Grok system.
After running a check, it found some issues.
So, it will then make the necessary changes.
So, I just gave it one prompt.
and then I selected the /goal command.
In the end, it took almost 42 minutes to help me out.
to complete at least 95% of the work for this app.
And the quality of the work was actually pretty impressive.
And in those 41 minutes, it consumed 741,000 tokens.
So, that's everything I wanted to cover today.
So, I started by talking about Fish Audio's S2.1 Pro, which is now free for developers.
starting with the TTS API.
Then, I introduced the open-source VOXWEAVER studio that I developed.
VOXWEAVER Studio.
Then, I shared how I first discussed the plan with the AI.
And then, I used Grok CLI to actually build the application.
I also went over some of the common keyboard shortcuts for Grok,
and the common slash commands.
I also showed some of my conversations with Grok.
and how it's coming along.
I'll put this Grok documentation in my community feed.
So if you're interested, you can definitely check it out.
Of course, by the time you're watching this video,
And this project will be open-source as well.
I hope you found this video helpful.
See you next time!